

Cyril Tulyakov QA Engineer

Details

Saint Petersburg Russia Federation

Phone

+7-960-595-1587

Email

cyril.tulyakov@yandex.ru kirill.tulyakov231@gmail.com

Date of birth 18.07.2000

Skills & Tools

Theory of testing(based on The Art of Software Testing 3rd Edition G.Myers)

Realtime rendering(based on Real-Time Rendering 4th Edition E. Haines)

Python

Django

C++

 \mathbf{C}

HTML&CSS

Bootstrap

Profile

At the moment, my main focus is QA in the rendering and technical field of games and engines. I started my way in development with the Yandex. Auto project in the company of the same name. After gaining experience, I moved to my first commercial game dev project WoWS:L (xbox, ps, mobile). At first, I was mainly engaged in technical tasks, to a lesser extent in gameplay. As a result, rendering and technical areas have become the main ones for me, where I am interested in researching and developing theory, methods and development tools, including testing.

Experience

Middle QA Engineer, Lesta Studio, Saint Petersburg MAY 2021 - PRESENT

Junior QA Engineer May 2021 - Oct 2021: mainly performed technical tasks, to a lesser extent gameplay tasks.

Middle QA Engineer Oct 2021 - Present: the main direction was the render direction and performance analysis, an additional tech direction.

Project World of Warships: Legends:

- Testing the project for console and mobile platforms
- Testing the BigWorld game engine
- Technical task testing management
- Project source code management (version control)
- Performance testing and analysis
- Testing the render/tech part of the project(Vulkan, GLES, Metal, D3D12, GNM, AGC)
- Testing the platform part of the project
- Testing the gameplay part of the project
- Development of the test base of the project
- Maintaining test and project documentation
- Development of auxiliary utilities for testing in Python

Tools: Jira, TestRail, Confluence, SVN, BitBucket, Teamcity, Jenkins, Perfana, Android Studio, Android SDK, 3uTools, MS Visual Studio, PyCharm, Xbox One Manager XDK/GDK, Neighbothhood for PS4, Target Manager for PS5, RAD Telemetry, ICAT, RenderDoc, Vulkan SDK, AGI

Public information about the project:

- https://wowslegends.com/blogs/entry/512-wows-legends-goes-mobile/
- https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zwyRErbTWJ4
- https://www.metacritic.com/game/playstation-4/world-of-warships-legends

SQL Bash Linux Git **SVN** Android SDK(Android studio/ADB) Vulkan SDK RenderDoc **RAD Telemetry** AGI(Android GPU Inspector) Xbox One Manager XDK/GDK Neighbothhood for PS4 Target Manager for PS5 Postman Task/bag-tracking system Test management system CI/CD **TestRail TeamCity** Jenkins GitLab Languages English(B1)

Links

Junior QA Engineer, Yandex, Remote

APRIL 2020 - APRIL 2021

Project Yandex.Auto(including Alice, Ya.Music, Ya.Navigator):

 Manual system testing of head units for cars on the Android platform(aftermarket, carsharing, OEM)

https://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-one/world-of-warships-legends

- Maintaining test and project documentation
- Development of test cases
- Working with the task management system (Yandex Tracker)
- Working with the test management system(TestPalm)
- Development of utilities for testing on Bash, Python(Win, OS X, Linux)
- Working with Postman
- Working with BitBucket

Tools: Yandex Tracker, TestPalm, Bitbucket, Teamcity, Android Studio, XCode, Android SDK, Postman

Public information about the project:

- https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ldNJpvbxBGk
- https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZdU5Bz3EHT0
- https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xU3wToQ368A
- https://www.lada.ru/enjoy-pro/

Education

Bachelor, TULA BRANCH OF THE FINANCIAL UNIVERSITY UNDER THE GOVERNMENT OF THE RUSSIAN FEDERATION, Tula

SEPTEMBER 2018 - MAY 2022

Course of study 38.03.05 Business informatics

IT management in business:

- Project management
- ERP System
- Python
- R
- SQL and DBMS

Internship

QA Engineer, Lesta Studio, Saint Petersburg

GitHub sunbro1337

Hobbies

The main hobbies are RPG(Action RPG, JRPG, MMORPG, Turn-based and Tactical RPG) and Action(Shooter, Platformer) games. I am also interested in tabletop role-play and wargame games. I have a musical education (piano, guitar), knowledge in the field of sound engineering. I study and analyze music of various genres, including game soundtracks.

MART 2022 - MAY 2022

Course of study 38.03.05 Business informatics

IT management in business:

- Project management
- ERP System
- Python
- R
- SQL and DBMS

Educational and industrial (including pre-graduate) practice was completed within the framework of obtaining an academic bachelor's degree in the field of training 38.03.05 Business Informatics:

- The basic concepts and principles of software development are studied
- The analysis of the testing management systems presented on the world market is carried out
- The analysis of remote Git repositories presented on the world market is carried out
- The analysis of the testing process and the description of problems is carried out
- The concept of "Test management via Git" is formulated
- The "CaseSync" software system has been developed
- The efficiency analysis of the developed "CaseSync" system is carried out
- The list of prospects for further development of the CaseSync system is formulated